ideone.com 2019-11-10

# Online Compiler and IDE >> C/C++, Java, PHP, Python, Perl and 70+ other compilers and interpreters - Ideone.com

* This Privacy and Cookie Policy defines the terms of gathering, processing and using personal data of the Users of the web-based Service available under the following web address ideone.com (hereinafter referred to as the “Service”). Controller of the personal data shall use best efforts to ensure that the privacy of Users of the Service is respected and that the personal information they disclose is protected.

* The Controller of the personal data and Administrator of the Service is Research Labs Sp. z o.o. (Limited) with its registered office in Gdynia, registered within the National Court Register held by the Regional Court for Gdańsk – North in Gdańsk, 8th Commercial Division of the National Court Register, under KRS no. 0000316381, VAT no. (NIP) 5862219354, REGON 220631894, with share capital of 70,300 PLN (hereinafter referred to as “SRL” or the “Controller”).

* Controller complies with its obligations under the GDPR by keeping personal data up to date; by storing and destroying it securely; by not collecting or retaining excessive amounts of data; by protecting personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access and disclosure and by ensuring that appropriate technical measures are in place to protect personal data.

* Controller gathers only the personal data which the User provides voluntarily. We may collect the following information:

  * first and last name,
  * e-mail address,

* The Personal Data will be collected, processed and used by us for the following purposes:

  * To performance of the contract.
  * To improve our products and support.
  * To sending you notifications related to the operation of the system.
  * To the delivery of marketing emails, which you have specifically requested
  * To contact via surveys to conduct research about their opinions of current services or of potential new services.

* We keep your personal data as long as you use the Service or your account is valid.

* Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and The Data Protection Act 2018 (DPA) you have a number of rights with regard to your personal data.

  * You have the right to request from us access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data, the right to restrict processing, object to processing as well as in certain circumstances the right to data portability. The User should use the correct tabs within the Service or send an e-mail message to the contact address indicated on the web site of the Service.
  * You have the right to withdraw consent at any time, if consent is the ground used for processing.
  * You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

* Personal data of Users is not used in automated decision-making algorithms.

* The User may agree for their personal data to be processed by the Controller of the personal data for marketing and commercial purposes. Although it is not a condition for using the Service.

* Each User of the Service may choose if and in what scope they want to use the Service and share their personal information.

* Personal data of Users is not disclosed to any third parties. Controller of the personal data does not store the Users’ confidential personal data such as credit card numbers or information allowing access to their bank accounts.

* Controller of personal data shares personal data of Users necessary to distribute the newsletter with an external entity on the basis of a written personal data sharing agreement.

* Controller of personal data shares personal data of Users necessary to create accounts within the Service (hosting) with an external entity on the basis of a written personal data sharing agreement.

* The Service does not automatically collect any information except for the information included in the cookie files.

* With respect for the provisions of the law and the Act on personal data protection, Administrator of the Service ensures security and maintains confidentiality of the obtained personal data.

* Cookie files (the so called cookies) are information files, particularly text files, which are stored on the device of the end User of the Service with the purpose of making it possible to use the Service. Cookies usually include the name of the website which they originate from, information regarding the period for which they are to be stored on the User’s device and a unique number.

* The entity which places cookie files on the end User’s device and which gains access to those files, is the operator of the ideone.com Service – Service is Research Labs Sp. z o.o. (Limited)) with its registered address in Gdynia.

* Cookie files are used for the following purposes:

  * to adapt the content of the Service website to the preferences of the User and to optimize the process of using those websites; particularly, the files allow for the User’s device to be recognized and for the website to be displayed properly, in accordance with the User’s individual preferences;
  * to gather statistical data, which helps us understand how Users browse through websites, which makes it possible for those websites to be improved in terms of their structure and content;
  * to maintain User sessions within the Service (after logging in), so that the User does not have to log in again on each sub-page of the Service using their username and password.

* There are two basic kinds of cookie files generated by the Service: “session cookies” and “persistent cookies”. Session cookies are temporary files, which are stored on the end User’s device until the user logs our, leaves the website or closes the browser window. Persistent cookies are stored within the end User’s device for a defined period of time, which is indicated within the parameters of the cookie file, or until they are removed by the User.

* The Service utilizes the following types of cookie files:

  * “required” cookies, which make it possible to use the Service, e.g. authorization cookies used for the services which require authorization within the Service;
  * cookie files which have the purpose of providing security, e.g. they are used to detect any malicious activity within the scope of authorization within the Service;
  * performance cookie files, which help in the process of gathering information regarding the way the websites of the Service are used;
  * functional cookie files, which make it possible to store the User’s selected settings and information regarding personalization of the User interface, e.g. in the scope of the selected language or region, where the User is located, size of the font, design of the web site etc.;
  * advertising cookie files, which make it possible to present Users with advertising content more suitable to their preference.
